{
    "subject": "Marie_Jos\u00e9_of_Belgium",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Umberto_II_of_Italy",
    "human_readable": "Marie Jos\u00e9 of Belgium is married to Umberto II of Italy.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9690104126930237,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Marie Jos\u00e9 of Belgium and Umberto II of Italy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9545099139213562,
            "question": "Who is Marie Jos\u00e9 of Belgium married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8290666341781616,
            "question": "In what century were Marie Jos\u00e9 and Umberto married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7705991268157959,
            "question": "What was the name of the former monarch whose wife was Marie Jos\u00e9 of Belgium?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7534659504890442,
            "question": "Who is Umberto II of Italy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6423624753952026,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Umberto II of Italy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6356132626533508,
            "question": "To which royal family does Marie Jos\u00e9 of Belgium belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5646501183509827,
            "question": "To which country does Marie Jos\u00e9 belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4040590226650238,
            "question": "Was Marie Jos\u00e9 a queen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3261859714984894,
            "question": "Which country did Umberto II rule?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Marie Jos\u00e9 of Belgium is married to Umberto II of Italy.",
            "html": "yago_5068_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Marie Jos\u00e9 a queen?",
            "html": "yago_5068_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which country does Marie Jos\u00e9 belong?",
            "html": "yago_5068_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which royal family does Marie Jos\u00e9 of Belgium belong?",
            "html": "yago_5068_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5068_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5068_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5068_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5068_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5068_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5068_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5068_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5068_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5068_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5068_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation result:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple pieces of information that support the triple, including:\n\n* The text of file_path:/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_5068/re-ranker-msmarco/12.txt, which mentions the marriage of Marie Jos\u00e9 of Belgium with Umberto II of Savoy on January 8, 1930.\n* The caption in file_path:/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_5068/re-ranker-msmarco/20.txt, which describes Prince Umberto II of Italy and his wife, Princess Marie Jose of Belgium.\n* The article in file_path:/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_5068/re-ranker-msmarco/48.txt, which states that Marie Jos\u00e9 married Crown Prince Umberto of Italy in 1930.\n\nAll these pieces of information confirm the marriage between Marie Jos\u00e9 of Belgium and Umberto II of Italy."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the marriage between Umberto II of Italy and Marie Jos\u00e9 of Belgium, with specific details such as the date (January 8, 1930) and other related events. Therefore, the statement that Marie Jos\u00e9 of Belgium is married to Umberto II of Italy is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}